Kyle Jarnagin

IT Administrator

WWW.JARNAGOOSE.COM

I'm Kyle Jarnagin, an IT Administrator and Certified Scrum Master with several years of experience in systems development, testing, implementation, and management. The breadth of my job responsibilities over the years have given me experience and perspectives that would otherwise not be typical in my position.

I have a passion for using the Scrum framework to break down complicated problems into workable solutions. There is no request that can't be solved through dedication and empiricism.

In my spare time when I'm not developing or working on my computer I'm an amateur mycologist and enjoy being out in the swamp or on the trails looking for mushrooms and molds.

Email: kylejads@gmail.com Number: (352) 222-2327

EDUCATION

University of South Florida 2018

B.A. of Communication Sciences & Disorders

Focused on the socio-linguistic differences between manual languages and English, and the impacts of mental and physical disabilities on the ability to communicate.

University of South Florida 2018

B.A. of Mass Communications

Developed skills for project management, learning systems design, and the psychology of advertising. Founded a student organization focused on the preservation of public art.

University of South Florida 2018
Certificate of Visualization and Design

Learned the entirety of the Adobe Creative Suite for use in the business world. Worked with local artists and photographers to develop installations with modern design.

University of South Florida 2016
Honors Dissertation

My co-investigator and I performed research in the greater Tampa Bay Area documenting discrimination experienced by deaf and hard-of-hearing individuals.

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Programming

Boxing

· Graphic Design

Knitting

Reading

• Knitting

Reading

• Illustration

Painting

Music

Gardening

......

Cooking

Sketching
Animation

SKILLS

Databases	Novice Adept Expert	UX/UI	Novice Adept Expert
Adobe Suite	Novice Adept Expert	Power BI	Novice Adept Expert
Bulk Mail	Novice Adept Expert	Data Analytics	Novice Adept Expert
CMS/LMS	Novice Adept Expert	Scrum	Novice Adept Expert
HTML/CSS/JS	Novice Adept Expert	Python	Novice Adept Expert
Office365	Novice Adept Expert	Power Platforms	Novice Adept Expert
Excel	Novice Adept Expert	Technical Writing	Novice Adept Expert

WORK HISTORY

Department of Health
May 2020 - Present

Senior Web Specialist

- Administrator for Florida Department of Health's (DOH) Office365 environment, provided support and development services across various Microsoft applications, specialized in Teams, SharePoint, Power BI, and Power Platforms.
- Administrator for DOH Content Management System CMS. Performed development, maintenance, user acceptance testing, and accessibility reviews.
- Administrator and implementation specialist for the DOH bulk mailer response system. Responsible for onboarding users and provided training and support during Hurrican Ian.
- ShareGate Administrator, performed content migrations and permissions audits.
- Database Administrator for the DOH domain database. Migrated and modernized outdated databases into the Office365 online ecosystem.
- Teams Administrator, responsible for onboarding users statewide and moving to a work from home response during the Covid-19 pandemic.
- Participated in planning, implementation, and maintenance of Department web development solutions, tools and support services.
- Developed and monitored hardware and software in cooperation with other state entities to ensure quality and continuity of service.
- Contributed to system and application planning, analysis, and design.
- · Managed projects utilizing Predictive and Scrum methodologies.

Department of Health Nov 2018 - May 2020 Operations Analyst

- CMS Manager, responsible for ensuring DOH sites were accessible and met WCAG 2.0 guidelines. Approved workflows, created websites, and performed security audits on users.
- SharePoint Administrator, authenticated and appointed user security groups to maintain user access.
- Training coordinator, developed IOP's and governance documents based on legislative guidelines.

Jarnagoose Creative Graphic Designer Jan 2017 - Present

- Created art using a python based neural network, used open-source resources to train models based on my own art style.
- Worked alongside local artists across Florida to provide the technical support and computer requirements for their installation art, utilized tools such as Adobe After-Effects, Premiere, Lightroom, Photoshop, Audacity, worked with projectors, light strips, screens, and audio devices.

